wildtangent.com 2012-11-22

# Games | Play Games Online | WildTangent Games

### OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage, the Games APP, and, in general, at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Please understand that by accessing or using the WildTangent Network you are agreeing with the privacy policy terms. As a result, we encourage you to read this entire Privacy Policy. If at any time you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us here.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT and HOW is it USED?

**_Sites and Games App  _**On some pages, you can play, rent and purchase games and other products, register and/or create a user profile, make requests, submit resume information, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include; name, address, email address, phone number, credit/debit card information, as well as other similar personal information.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you may need to submit the recipient's email and/or mailing address. In these circumstances, the types of personal information collected may be; name, address, phone number, and/or email address.

We do store your personally identifiable information in a secure manner, and also use Secure Sockets Layer encrypted connections to transmit your payment-related personally identifiable information to further protect its privacy. We may also collect unique usage information, which does NOT include personally identifiable information, to assist us in understanding our customers' use patterns and for use in developing new products and services.

**_Games  _**When you play a game on the WildTangent Network, WildTangent collects certain profile information that you provide directly.  We collect information related to your spending of WildCoins, and we may automatically collect information about your game play and interactions with other players in a social game.  Otherwise, games we operate on the WildTangent Network do NOT collect personally identifiable information without your consent.  Please note that some of the games you may find on the WildTangent Network may be operated by a third party (for example, some massively multiplayer online games) and your use of such games will be subject to the privacy policy of such third party.

 ** _Aggregated and Anonymous Data  _**We may also collect unique device usage information, which does NOT include personally identifiable information, to assist us in understanding our customers' use patterns and for use in developing new products and services. To facilitate the operation of the Games App, it will collect and report anonymous information necessary to ensure reliable delivery of downloaded games and game content. This information may include data about whether or not content download and installation was successful, game session length (for trial versions), and Games App session length.  To help ensure that you have consistent, high quality experiences with our games, and to assist us with product development and planning, we do collect anonymous usage statistics. We do this by assigning a unique identifier in our databases that is NOT linked to any of your personal information. The information gathered is used to accurately count the number of people using our games and other content successfully and is also NOT linked to any of your personal information. At times we may share this usage information with third parties, but only in an anonymous aggregated form - that is, we collect usage information about the thousands of times our games are played, and analyze it as a whole.

**_Social Networks  _**When you access any game on the WildTangent Network at a social network (for example, Facebook), you permit WildTangent to access certain information from your profile on that social network, depending on the game, as well as the privacy settings you have established for that social network.  By playing a game on the WildTangent Network through a social network, you are authorizing WildTangent to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network could provide to WildTangent through the social network application programming interface.

**_Mobile  _**If you play games on the WildTangent Network on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, we collect your unique device identifier and may collect your telephone number, country, and other information you choose to provide, such as user name, character name, location or email address.

_**Support  **_When you request support from us by email, on the telephone, through our web support portal, or by other means we may provide, we will collect and store the contact information you provide (generally your name and e-mail address), information about your game play or activity on the WildTangent Network, any registration numbers you provide, as well as the communications between us over such support issue.

**_With Whom Do We Share Personal Information?_**

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent (subject to the limited exceptions identified below) and at the time you are asked for this information or for consent, we will inform you of: 

  * The personally identifiable information to be shared
  * The identity of the third party
  * A link to the third party's privacy statement, if available 

Please understand that we may also share your information with third parties under the following limited circumstances and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy: 

  * If we need to process a transaction you have placed with us on the WildTangent Network, such as purchasing a game or a digital item.  For example, if you pay by a credit or debit card, your card number and sales transaction information are passed on to the card processor and/or issuer (including their service providers such as fraud verification services), and if you request shipment for a purchase, we may provide your address to the shipping carrier.
  * If we use third party contractors to provide services to us or on our behalf. For example, we might retain a company to process credit card payments, to email information about special offers, or to analyze data.  We do require such contractors to maintain personally identifiable information as confidential, and to only use it on our behalf.
  * If we, in good faith, are required to disclose it to comply with legal processes, or we need to do so to protect your, our or the public's rights or property interests.
  * If our company is involved in a sale, merger, or any other combination with a third party. In such circumstances, the surviving entity will be responsible for this Privacy Policy and the personally identifiable information collected from you.

**_Does WildTangent Use Passive Means To Collect Information?_**

To permit your efficient use of the WildTangent Network, we use cookies (small files stored in your computer), which let us know how you accessed us and let us know that you are a prior customer (so that you will not have to re-enter all of the information previously provided to us every time you access our sites). Please note that cookies are not used to access your payment information. This information can only be accessed when you enter your name and password. 

We (or third parties on our behalf) may also use web beacons, or similar technologies, which are transparent images that have been placed on a web page or an e-mail message, and send a signal that allows us to determine when a page has been visited, or an e-mail opened. Web beacons or similar technologies do not contain or collect personally identifiable information. The information that we do collect is used to allow us to better understand our customers' usage patterns, and to help us determine how they accessed our website(s). This information, in turn, allows us to improve our products to better meet your needs, and to enhance our communications with you. 

**_Are there other Parties Collecting Information about me that I should be aware of while using the WildTangent Network?_**

**_Other Third Party Sites  _**The WildTangent Network may be linked to Internet websites or other platforms operated by other companies. Some of these websites or other platforms may be co-branded with our name or logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by us. WildTangent is not responsible for the privacy practices of the websites or other platforms operated by third parties. Once you have left the Sites, you should check the privacy policy of the other website or platform to determine how it handles any personally identifiable information it collects from you.  Please be aware that WildTangent does not warn you when you have chosen to link through to another website or property from the Sites.

 ** _Advertisers and Ad Network  _** WildTangent carries advertisements on the WildTangent Network. Some of these ads are served by WildTangent, and some are served by third party ad networks. Where an ad is served by WildTangent that requests personal information from you (for example, in a survey), WildTangent collects the personal information you disclose, along with the advertiser and/or ad network. Otherwise, WildTangent does not collect personal information from such ads.  

Some ads may provide the ability to click through to websites or properties run by the advertiser or other third parties or to otherwise interact with an advertiser, sometimes without even leaving the Sites. WildTangent is not responsible for the privacy practices of advertisers. Once you have clicked on an advertisement, you should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to determine how it handles any personally identifiable information it collects from you. 

Ad networks and other third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to various websites other than the WildTangent Network. WildTangent does not have control over cookies, web beacons or other technologies that such third parties may use, but WildTangent may acquire non-personally identifiable information regarding the behavior and usage patterns of users of websites and other online properties from third parties, and also may combine this information with other non-personally identifiable information we have collected, to deliver advertisements to you, measure the effectiveness of ads, and more effectively target advertisements and offerings that may be of greater interest to you.  We are not responsible for the information collection practices of other third party websites that you may visit.  Some of these third party websites and advertising companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") or may be partners with information aggregators, such as BlueKai, and may permit you to opt out of tracking by participating websites.  While WildTangent is not responsible for the terms of these organizations or the effectiveness of their opt out procedures, for more information on opting out of tracking mechanisms, please see, for example, the BlueKai website at <http://www.bluekai.com/consumers_optout.php> or the NAI opt-out tool at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**_Other Third Parties_**  WildTangent, or third party advertisers, may use third party research firms to conduct brand studies or perform other analytics, and such third party research firms may also use cookies or use beacons to gather relevant information, including whether a user has or has not seen a particular ad campaign.

**_Do You Provide Ongoing Product Updates Or Other Information?_**

Periodically, we may send e-mails or text messages to users of our products and services with news, updates, special offers and other information relating to our products and services, and to select third party products and services. You may opt out of receiving these communications by accessing your account information through the My Account section of the Sites or the Game App, or by clicking on the link provided at the bottom of our e-mails to you. 

**_What Happens If I Decline To Provide Personal Information Or Remove Or Reject Passive Information Gathering?_**

If you choose not to submit personal information, or if you choose to configure your browser to remove or reject cookies or other passive data collection, you will not be able to fully utilize our products, services and website features (for example, you will not be able to store items in your shopping cart or complete a game purchase, or you may not be able to receive digital items provided by an advertiser). 

**_How do we Protect the Information we Collect?_**

We use reasonable physical, technical, and administrative measures to safeguard personally identifiable information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. For example, passwords and other sensitive information are encrypted in transit. We also take steps to ensure that only those WildTangent employees, agents, and contractors who have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your personally identifiable information are granted access.

When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information), we encrypt that information using secure sockets layering technology (SSL), an industry standard protocol for billing transmission in order to protect the financial information you send us. We store your payment information in encrypted form. 

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of the Sites and our customer databases and records, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We want you to feel confident using the WildTangent Network but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Please refer to the U.S. Federal Trade Commission's website for information on how to protect yourself from identity theft.

**_What is our Commitment To Children's Privacy?_**

The WildTangent Network is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13.  WildTangent does not permit the registration on the Sites by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age.  In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, we will take reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records. 

**_How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information?_**

If you wish to review, update or delete any personal information that we have collected about you, please contact us here, or by regular mail at: WildTangent, c/o Privacy Officer, 18578 NE 67th Court, Building 5, Redmond, WA 98052. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**_How Do I Learn About Changes To This Privacy Policy?_**

We may periodically update our Privacy Policy. Please understand that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently to remain informed about any changes to it. Your continued use of the WildTangent Network will indicate your acceptance of any changes we do make. Our most current Privacy Policy will always be available for your review on http://www.wildtangent.com/privacy.

**_Can I Opt Out of Receiving Updates?_**

You may opt out of receiving alerts or email or text message updates concerning the WildTangent Network. We also will not share your personally identifiable information with advertisers, business partners, or other entities that are not affiliated with WildTangent who would like to send you promotional information about their products and services directly, unless you have opted in to sharing such information.  But we may send you administrative email or text messages, service announcements, terms and conditions of your account(s), or other similar communications, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. This is important in case we need to communicate with you about items such as your account, billing, payments, terms of use, pricing changes, and other non-promotional matters. 

**_How to contact us_**

 ** __**We encourage your questions and comments about any privacy concerns, about this Privacy Policy, or about any of our products and services. Please direct them to us by contactingcustomer service or through regular mail to: WildTangent c/o Privacy Officer, 18578 NE 67th Court, Building 5, Redmond, WA 98052. Additional information about WildTangent is also available at www.wildtangent.com.

**_How do you Resolve Dispute?_**

Should a customer ever have a privacy complaint, WildTangent has agreed to participate in the Better Business Bureau's Privacy Dispute Resolution system. More information about this program may be obtained at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints>

**_Do you Participate in the E.U. Safe Harbor Program?_**

WildTangent is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor website. You may also contact us directly about the Safe Harbor program if you would like more information.

Privacy Policy Last Updated March 31, 2011
